{
    "questions": [
        {
          "question": "Which technology is used in cricket to know the speed of the ball?",
          "statement": "Choose the correct option",
          "answers": [
            "Ultrasonic technology",
            "Radar technology",
            "The Hawk Eye technology",
            "GPS technology"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": 2
        },
        {
          "question": "Which tech is used in cricket to know whether the bat and ball are contacted in an appeal of caught behind and LBW?",
          "statement": "Choose the correct option",
          "answers": [
            "Snickometer",
            "UltraEdge",
            "Stump mic",
            "Hot Spot"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": 1
        },
        {
          "question": "Which tech is used by FIFA for offside decisions in football?",
          "statement": "Choose the correct option",
          "answers": [
            "VAR",
            "GLT",
            "SAOT (Uses Hawk-eye cameras)",
            "Aerial camera"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": 2
        },
        {
          "question": "What is a compression algorithm? Take reference from the TV show \"The Silicon Valley\".",
          "statement": "Choose the correct option",
          "answers": [
            "A protocol for internet communication",
            "A tool for database management",
            "A type of virus scanner",
            "A method to compress large video files"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": 3
        },
        {
          "question": "What is the best solution when the system goes down as per the TV show \"The IT Crowd\"?",
          "statement": "Choose the correct option",
          "answers": [
            "Reinstall the operating system",
            "Upgrade the hardware",
            "Update the drivers",
            "Try turning it off and on again"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": 3
        },
        {
          "question": "How is data profiling used in targeted advertising with reference to the TV show \"The Great Hack\"?",
          "statement": "Choose the correct option",
          "answers": [
            "To create targeted advertising campaigns",
            "To hack into social media accounts",
            "To steal credit card information",
            "To create fake social media accounts"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": 0
        },
        {
          "question": "What was the name of the voice of AI in the movie \"Her\"?",
          "statement": "Choose the correct option",
          "answers": [
            "Scarlett Johansson",
            "Emma Stone",
            "Natalie Portman",
            "Jennifer Lawrence"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": 0
        },
        {
          "question": "In the movie \"Interstellar,\" what is the name of the advanced AI robot and what is it used for?",
          "statement": "Choose the correct option",
          "answers": [
            "HAL 9000, used for space exploration",
            "WALL-E, used for cleaning space debris",
            "TARS, used for space exploration",
            "C-3PO, used for translation"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": 2
        },
        {
          "question": "In the 2008 movie \"Ghajini,\" the protagonist, played by Aamir Khan, uses a unique system to keep track of his memories. What was the technology?",
          "statement": "Choose the correct option",
          "answers": [
            "Polaroid pictures",
            "Video recordings",
            "Voice recordings",
            "Written notes"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": 0
        },
        {
          "question": "How do Transformers change their shape and size from their robot form to their vehicle form and vice versa?",
          "statement": "Choose the correct option",
          "answers": [
            "Through the use of magic",
            "By shrinking and expanding their metal frame",
            "Through a series of articulated joints and movable parts",
            "By using a special transformation serum"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": 2
        },
        {
          "question": "What is the technology behind Doraemon's magical gadget Bamboo-Copter?",
          "statement": "Choose the correct option",
          "answers": [
            "Solar energy",
            "Wind power",
            "Spinning the leaves at a high speed",
            "A magic spell"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": 2
        },
        {
          "question": "What is the name of the device that Phineas and Ferb invent to make themselves younger in the episode \"Doof Dynasty\"?",
          "statement": "Choose the correct option",
          "answers": [
            "The Age-Decelerator-inator",
            "The Youth-Enrichment Machine",
            "The Anti-Aging Device",
            "The Age-Accelerator-inator"
          ],
          "correctAnswer": 3
        }
      ]
}